http://www.aium.org/misc/privacyPolicy.aspx

By using this website, you agree to our use of cookies. AIUM uses cookies to provide you with a better user experience and to help our website run effectively. See our Privacy
Policy for more details.
About Us
LeadershipHistoryAwardsCommitteesMission & Constitution
Join/RenewCommunities
Basic Science and InstrumentationCardiovascular UltrasoundContrast-Enhanced UltrasoundDermatologyElastographyFetal EchocardiographyGeneral and Abdominal UltrasoundGynecologic UltrasoundHigh Frequency Clinical and Preclinical ImagingInterventional-Intraoperative UltrasoundMusculoskeletal UltrasoundNeurosonologyObstetric UltrasoundPediatric UltrasoundPoint-of-Care UltrasoundSonographyTherapeutic UltrasoundUltrasound in Global HealthUltrasound in Medical EducationUrology
Learning Center
CME TrackerUpcoming WebinarsOn-Demand Webinars and LecturesJournal ArticlesAIUM Courses & EventsPast ConventionsAccreditation & Disclosures
Resources
Practice ParametersCase ChallengeTraining GuidelinesOfficial StatementsUltrasound in Med Ed PortalResource LibraryTeaching ToolsCareersRelated SitesUltrasound Awareness (MUAM)Member Directory (Members Only)
Accreditation
Application InstructionsFrequently Asked QuestionsAccess Accreditation AccountAccredited Practice ResourcesDirectory of Accredited Practices
Future Fund
AIUM Future Fund
Journal
Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement
The AIUM recognizes the importance of protecting the personal information collected from users in the operation of its services and takes reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to the AIUM you consent to the practices described in this policy. If you are less than 18 years of age, then you must first seek the consent of your parent or guardian prior to submitting any personal information. We reserve the right to modify this statement at any time, so please check back periodically for our latest privacy practices.
Collection of Information
Personal identifying information is your name, street or email address, phone number or any other information when used by itself or with other data, might identify you individually. The AIUM does not collect this information on this website except where it is sent to us voluntarily.
Use of Information
The AIUM may use the personal identifying information we collect to contact you in the future. Specifically, we may send promotional emails notifying you of events, products and services, significant developments, or other information we believe might be of interest. Once someone voluntarily provides an email address, the AIUM uses that information to email the person for transaction follow-up, promotions and communications. We collect data to track the effectiveness of emails, which enables us to better serve our varied audiences. This information includes browser, operating system, device type, IP address, pages viewed, and length of time on site.
This information is collected through third-party cookies and non-cookie technologies. This information may be shared with third-party AIUM partners, such as NextRoll, to serve targeted advertising and for measurement and analytics. The AIUM may rent mailing addresses to third parties. These third parties may subsequently contact you by mail.
Opt Out
All AIUM marketing emails include a link for unsubscribing. If you do not wish to have your personal identifying information used or disclosed for these purposes, you may "opt-out." You can learn about how to opt out of receiving targeted advertising here.
European Union Residents Only
If you are a European Union resident and wish to have your personal information removed from our systems entirely and permanently, please contact us at admin@aium.org to initiate the process. Please keep in mind this is irreversible and we will not be able to recover your previous membership terms or any other past records if you wish to rejoin or become a customer in the future.
Notwithstanding any of the above, we may release membership lists or personal identifying information if we determine the release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our contractual rights or obligations, to protect the rights, property, or safety of the AIUM, our members, or others, or to establish a legal claim or defense.
California Residents
Additional privacy information for California residents can be found here.
Security
We use appropriate physical, technical and administrative safeguards to protect your data. We collect the minimum information necessary to fulfill our goods and services, such as becoming a member, purchasing a product, or registering for a course or event. Multiple layers of physical, administrative, and electronic protections have been put in place to protect all information from unauthorized use, access, or malicious activity. Access to your personal data is restricted to only those who need to know that information and required to perform their job function.
